Guide to the Vassar College Postcard Collection, circa 1899 - circa 1982
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Postcard Collection
circa 1899 - circa 1982
Vassar College
1 cubic foot (5 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
This collection consists of postcards featuring Vassar College's campus, buildings, students, and events, as well as some postcards of Poughkeepsie, New York; Silver Bay, New York; and Vassar, Michigan.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of postcards featuring Vassar College's campus, buildings, students, and events, as well as some postcards of Poughkeepsie, New York; Silver Bay, New York; and Vassar, Michigan.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by subject.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Buildings; Vassar College--Description--Views; Vassar College--Students
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Places:
Poughkeepsie (N.Y.)--Description--Views; Silver Bay (N.Y.)--Description--Views; Vassar (Mich.)--Description--Views
Document Types:
Photographs; Postcards
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Audiovisuals and Realia
Encoding Information
Encoded by Emma Gronbeck, February 2025.
Acquisition Information
Gift of various donors.
Container List
- Alumnae Gymnasium (Ely Hall), 1901-1917, undated (Box 1)
- Alumnae House, 1938-1949, undated (Box 1)
- Athletic Circle, circa 1910-1926, undated (Box 1)
- Avery Hall (Museum and Art Gallery, Calisthenium and Riding Academy), 1906-1917, undated (Box 1)
- Blodgett Hall, undated (Box 1)
- Chapel, 1905-1918, undated (Box 1)
- Chicago Hall, undated (Box 1)
- The Conservatory, 1914-1918, undated (Box 1)
- Cushing House, 1945, undated (Box 1)
- Daisy Chain, 1907-1910, undated (Box 1)
- Davison Hall, 1907, undated (Box 1)
- Faculty Houses, 1954, undated (Box 1)
- Ferry House, undated (Box 1)
- Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center, undated (Box 1)
- Jewett Hall (North Hall), 1907-1914, undated (Box 1)
- Josselyn Hall, 1923, undated (Box 1)
- Kendrick House, undated (Box 1)
- Kenyon Hall, undated (Box 1)
- Lathrop Hall, 1905-1910, undated (Box 1)
- Library, Lockwood Addition, undated (Box 1)
- Library, Thompson (Horizontal), 1906-1915, undated (Box 1)
- Library, Thompson (Vertical), undated (Box 1)
- Library, Thompson (Oversize), undated (Box 5)
- Library, Thompson - Cornaro Window, undated (Box 1)
- Library, Thompson - Interior, undated (Box 1)
- Library, Thompson - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1)
- The Lodge (Vassar Main Gate), 1905-1913, undated (Box 1)
- Maid's Club House (Admissions Building), undated (Box 1)
- Main Building (from the Northwest), 1966, undated (Box 1)
- Main Building (from the Southwest), 1901-1919, undated (Box 1)
- Main Building (from the West), 1908-1937, undated (Box 1)
- Main Building (Oversize), undated (Box 5)
- Main Building - Fire, 1918 (Box 1)
- Main Building - Interior, undated (Box 1)
- Metcalf House, undated (Box 1)
- New England Building, 1944, undated (Box 1)
- Noyes House, undated (Box 1)
- Observatory, Maria Mitchell, 1901-1954, undated (Box 1)
- Olmstead Hall, [1973?] (Box 1)
- Outdoor Theater, undated (Box 1)
- Poughkeepsie, 1906-1913, undated (Box 1)
- Poughkeepsie - The Wagner Inn (College Inn, Vassar Inn), 1907-1913, undated (Box 1)
- President's House, 1909, undated (Box 1)
- The Quadrangle, undated (Box 1)
- Raymond Hall, 1905-1920, undated (Box 1)
- Raymond Hall (Oversize), undated (Box 5)
- Rockefeller Hall, 1901-1914, undated (Box 1)
- Sanders Chemistry Lab, undated (Box 1)
- Silver Bay, NY, undated (Box 1)
- Skinner Hall of Music, 1907-1915, undated (Box 1)
- Strong House, undated (Box 1)
- Students, 1899-1912, undated (Box 1)
- Students' Hall (ACDC), undated (Box 1)
- Summer Institute, undated (Box 1)
- Sunset Hill and Sunset Lake (Pratt Lake), 1914 - circa 1982, undated (Box 1)
- Swift Infirmary, 1907, undated (Box 1)
- Taylor Hall and Van Ingen Library Addition, 1915-1954, undated (Box 1)
- Vassar, Matthew, 1906, undated (Box 1)
- Vassar, Michigan (Town), undated (Box 1)
- Vassar Brothers Lab, undated (Box 1)
- Vassar Campus - Aerial, undated (Box 2)
- Vassar Campus - Aerial (Oversize), circa 1907 (Box 5)
- Vassar Campus - Aerial (Oversize), [circa 1926?] (Box 5)
- Vassar Campus - Gates, undated (Box 2)
- Vassar Campus Views (including Winter), undated (Box 2)
- Vassar Lake, undated (Box 2)
- Wagner Inn, undated (Box 2)
- Warden's House, undated (Box 2)
- Williams Hall, undated (Box 2)
- Wimpfheimer Nursery School, undated (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous, Postcard Sets, undated (Box 2)
- Duplicates, A-N, undated (Box 3)
- Duplicates, N-Z, undated (Box 4)